-我能问你一个问题吗  -能啊
- Hey, can I ask you a question? - Sure.
我刚认识你们时这飞镖靶就在这了
You've had this dart board since I've known you,
但我从没见你们玩过啊
but I've never seen you play.
我们玩过啊  就一次
Oh, uh, we played... once.
我把窗户弄破了
I broke a window.
-哪个窗户  -那边的那扇
- What window? - That one over there.
莱纳德  游乐场点卷上哪去了
Leonard, where are the Skee-Ball tickets?
什么点卷
Skee-Ball tickets?
我们三年前去游乐场时拿到的点卷啊
Yeah, from when we went to the arcade three years ago?
我想好我要换什么奖品了
I finally decided what prize I want.
快点啊
Hurry up.
如果我还有留着
Uh, if I still have them,
估计就放在这个垃圾收集盒里了
they're probably in the junk box.
你准备换什么呢
Ooh, what are you gonna get?
不关你的事
None of your business.
但如果之后你看到我的西装上
But when you see me wearing a flower
别了一朵花
in my lapel later,
欢迎你来闻闻
you are most welcome to sniff it.
找到了  给
Yup, oh... here you go.
谢啦
Oh, thank you.
去换个橡皮擦当你的辛苦费吧
Here, get yourself an eraser for your troubles.
我都忘了这东西
I forgot about this.
我要去上大学时  阿姨做给我的
My aunt made it for me when I started college.
她很讨厌你吗
Aw, did she hate you?
怎么会  是因为我拿到又丑又痒的毛衣
Why? Because I got an ugly, itchy sweater,
而我哥拿到一台车吗  她绝对"比较宠我"
and my brother got a car? No, I was her favorite.
好像少了几张票
Yeah, I seem to be a few tickets short.
盒子里还有吗
Are there more in the box?
应该都拿出来了吧
Hmm, I think I got them all.
没  里面没有了
Nope, they're not in there.
你都没仔细找  我来吧
Well, you barely looked. Let me see.
不用不用  我看过了
No, no, no, I-I looked, and...
里面没了
No more tickets.
莱纳德  让我看看
Leonard, let me look in the box.
别  别
Okay, okay!
我可以让你看箱子里有什么
I'm gonna show you what's in the box.
但你得答应你不能跳脚
but just... promise not to flip out.
我为什么会跳脚
Why would I flip out?
是里面有蜘蛛吗
Is it a spider?
有蜘蛛
It's a spider!
不会是蜘蛛啦
No, if it was a spider,
有的话小莱莱早跳脚了
Lenny would've flipped out.
谢尔顿
Okay, Sheldon,
我知道很久以前就该还这张DVD了
I know I was supposed to return this DVD a long time ago,
我也知道这是用你的卡去租的
and I know we rented it on your card.
但这都过去七年了
But it's been, like, seven years
也没有任何不良后果
and clearly nothing bad has happened.
所以...  与其跟平常一样
So in-in-in-instead of being
使劲找我麻烦
a giant pain in the ass like you always are,
何不就一次
what if this one time
你试着保持冷静呢
you just tried staying calm?
你这要求听起来颇为合理
That seems like a reasonable request.
但是我的要求也很合理  莱纳德兄
Although so did, "Hey, Leonard,
能否劳烦你去还个DVD呢
would you mind returning that DVD?"
我错了  我会去处理这事
I'm sorry. I'll-Ill take care of it.
好的
Okay.
真心的  我会去处理
I mean it, I'm going to.
我相信你啊
I believe you.
你也会不生气  保持冷静吗
And you're going to stay calm?
我说了我会
I said I would.
看到没
How about that?
谢尔顿居然讲理了
Sheldon's being reasonable.
对啊  有点吓到我了  我要走了
Yeah, it's freaking me out. I'm gonna go.
生活大爆炸
第七季  第八集
所以  当你说你
So... when you say
不会为DVD的事情气得跳脚时
you're not going to freak out about the DVD,
是指这些意思吧
here's what that means.
你不会揪住这事不放
Don't fixate on it.
也不会半夜把我闹醒
Don't wake me up in the middle of the night.
或我在上厕所时
Or nag me through the door
在门外烦我
while I'm on the toilet.
首先  在你上厕所时跟你说话
Okay, first, talking to you while you're on the toilet
对我来说也不是很愉快好吗
isn't exactly a picnic for me either, okay?
别忘了
Remember...
你听得到我的声音  我也听得到"你的"
when you can hear me, I can hear you.
第二
And second...
你完全忽视了
you completely disregard
悬而未决事情对我的闹心程度
how uncomfortable unresolved issues are for me.
那感觉就像...
It's-it's like, a...
我脑子里有个挠不到的痒痒
an itch in my brain I can't scratch.
我以前手臂打石膏时
When I broke my arm I used
痒了我就拿衣架子伸进去挠
to stick a coat hanger down there.
你试过吗  试试从你耳朵伸进去挠[请勿模仿]
You ever try that? Maybe go in through the ear?
如果你能理解我  你就不会还在开玩笑了
You wouldn't make jokes if you could feel the way I feel.
我不知道怎么理解你那感受啊
Well, I don't know how to do that.
这样吧
How about this?
我答应你不烦你这DVD的事
I promise I won't pester you about the DVD.
也还你清静的拉屎时光
You can defecate in peace.
这对我们也是双赢  但是...
That's a win for both of us. But...
在你处理完这事之前
until this matter is resolved,
我要你
I would like you
穿着这件毛衣
to wear this sweater.
而且底下不许穿任何衣服
With nothing underneath it.
这蠢爆了  为啥要我穿
That's stupid. Why?
你说这穿起来又痒又不舒服
You say it's itchy and uncomfortable.
我对这事的感受也正是如此
I say situations like this make me feel the same way.
信我的  试试用衣架子啊
I'm telling you, try the hanger.
穿上
Put it on.
体验体验我的感受
Let's share the experience.
满足你
You got it.
如果穿上这毛衣就能让你闭嘴
If this sweater shuts you up,
那我以后光卖这个
I'm gonna make a fortune
给我们认识的人  就能发大财
selling them to everyone we know.
现在
Now...
我只需要走到录像带店
all I need to do is head down to the video store
还了这DVD就行了
and return the DVD.
我忘了跟你说了吗
Oh, did I forget to tell you?
那家店几年前就倒闭了
That store went out of business years ago.
是吗
Really?
你的咪咪感觉如何啊  猛将兄
How those nipples feeling, chief?
佩妮  能麻烦你把喝的给我们吗
Penny, can we please get our drinks?
行  再等一下
Yeah, hang on, just give me sec.
今天上班时  我做了一起立体定向手术
At work today, I did an in vivo stereotaxic surgery.
厉害啊  今天在实验室
Cool. At my lab,
我做了十起激光捕获显微切割
I performed ten laser capture micro-dissections.
我今天就把桌子下面的口香糖刮下来了
I scraped gum off the bottom of that table.
因为我经理看见是我把它粘上去的
Only 'cause my manager saw me put it there.
天啊
Oh, my gosh.
那不是伤了拉杰什心的那个女孩吗
That's the girl that broke Rajesh's heart.
她就是露西啊
That's Lucy?
不知道为什么  我总是以为那个女是个印度人
I don't know why but I always pictured her as Indian.
因为你有种族歧视
I think that reason's called racism.
我要过去跟她说话
I'm gonna go talk to her.
为什么  你要说什么
Why? What are you gonna say?
我什么都不会说
I'm not gonna say anything.
我只是想探下她的口风
I just want to check her out.
因为她伤害了我的朋友
Because she hurt my friend.
我的印度朋友
My Indian friend.
-现在是谁种族歧视  -你啊
- Who's racist now? - You.
因为你刚称拉杰是你的"印度朋友"
Because you just called him your "Indian friend."
怎样  你个矮冬瓜
Yeah, well, you're short.
看来我们喝不上东西了
We're never getting our drinks.
是啊  但我们早就料到了
No, but we knew that.
你想先来点喝的吗
Hey, can I start you off with something to drink?
-来杯水吧  -好的
- Oh, water would be great. - Okay.
你是露西吧
Um, you're Lucy, right?
我是拉杰什·库萨帕里的朋友
I'm a friend of Raj Koothrappali's.
其实先认出你的是艾米
Actually Amy recognized you.
他现在怎么样
How's he doing?
还不错
Oh, you know, he's good.
很好
Great.
这虽然不关我的事
Yeah, this is none of my business.
但你为什么要用一封电邮跟他分手
But why did you break up with him in an e-mail?
我也不知道
Oh, I don't know.
可能当时我觉得这样轻松点吧
I guess I thought it would be easier.
好吧  我懂了
Yeah, I get that.
我去给你拿水
I'll go get you your water.
你刚说"轻松点"
When you say "easier,"
是指对你而言  对吧
you mean easier for you, right?
因为这对他而言  一点也不轻松
'Cause it certainly didn't make it easier for him.
我能换一个服务员吗
Any chance I can get a different waitress?
很抱歉  我失礼了
I-I'm sorry, this is rude of me.
我现在就给你拿水
I will go get that water.
瞧瞧  瞧瞧
See, see, see, see.
刚才你就当着我的面  表达了你的感受
Just now you expressed your feelings to my face.
为什么对我就可以  对拉杰就不行呢
How come you could do that with me, but not Raj?
因为我不知道你的邮箱
I don't know your e-mail.
你知道最糟糕的是什么吗
You know what the worst part is?
你坐在这里  喜眉笑眼
You're sitting here, perfectly happy
而他却窝在家  以泪洗面
and he's at home, a blubbering mess.
你刚不是说他过得还不错吗
Oh, I thought you said he was okay.
我还说给你端水过来呢
Well, I also said I was getting you water,
但我现在不还站在这教训你吗
but look at me still standing here.
或许我是个烂服务员
You know, I may be a bad waitress,
但你是个烂人
but you are a bad person.
对了  你想听听今晚的特餐吗
Now, you want to hear the specials?
你永远都不能脱下来吗
So, you can never take it off?
是的
No.
连睡觉都不行吗
Not even to sleep?
是的
No.
所以你就是一白痴嘛
So, you're just an idiot?
我是为了证明我的观点
It's called proving a point.
你的观点就是你的白痴吗
Is the point you're an idiot?
先生们  别这样嘛
Gentlemen, please.
莱纳德只是假设性穿着我的鞋  换位思考而已
Leonard is trying to walk a mile in my metaphorical shoes.
当然他不能真穿我的鞋子
He can't walk in my actual shoes.
因为他有双婴儿脚
He has the feet of a toddler.
如果那家店已经关门了
So, how are you gonna return the DVD
你要怎么把DVD还给人家
if the store went out of business?
周一上午我会去市中心一趟
Monday morning I'll go downtown
查一下店主的资料
look up the owner's information.
然后把DVD寄回去给他
And send him the DVD.
再把滞纳金交了
Pay the late fee.
同时向谢尔顿证明
And prove to Sheldon
在遇到问题和解决问题的过程中
that you can have a problem and solve it...
人不一定都要表现得像个十足的疯子
...without acting like a complete lunatic.
而那个假扮成熊的人会希望大家知道
And the man impersonating a bear would like everyone to know
护林熊身穿美国护林警服装的漫画熊
其身上印有"Only you can prevent forest fires"字样
"只有你能防止森林火灾"
that "Only you can prevent forest fires."
我没明白笑点
I don't get it.
-你们印度没有护林熊吗  -没有
- You didn't have Smokey the Bear in India? - No.
是不是像我们的獴狐猴
Oh, is he anything like, uh, Mun-Mun the Mongoose?
它教导我们不要跟眼镜蛇一起玩
He taught us not to play with cobras.
没人教你们就会去跟眼镜蛇玩吗
You had to be taught not to play with cobras?
没人教你们就会去烧森林吗
You had to be taught not to burn down the forest?
你们要是肚子饿
Hey, if you guys were hungry,
为什么在餐厅时不点东西吃呢
why didn't you order something at the restaurant?
我们点了啊  你没上菜而已
We did, you never brought it.
对哦
Oh, that's right.
玉米片与火鸡三明治
Nachos and a turkey club.
完全不对
Not even close.
那是因为我当时忙着在
Well, I was too busy standing up
为我们的朋友挺身而出  没空上...
for my friend to worry about your...
我想说是三文鱼吧
I want to say salmon.
你想说的应该是对不起
You want to say sorry.
所以你打算怎么跟拉杰解释你的行为
So, how are you gonna tell Raj abut what you did?
干嘛要想怎么解释  没什么大不了的
What do you mean "how"? What's the big deal?
你告诉露西他以泪洗面
You told Lucy he was a pathetic mess.
把人家都说到哭着跑了
Then you made her cry and leave.
够了  你们想得也太严重了
Okay, you guys are overreacting.
拉杰会感谢我为他挺身而出的
Raj is gonna appreciate how I had his back.
你脑子进水了吗  佩妮
What is wrong with you, Penny?!
你毁了我与她重修旧好的可能性
You ruined any chance I had of getting back with Lucy!
现在她知道我很悲催凄凉了
Now she knows I'm a desperate mess
她本来只能九成确定呢
instead of just being pretty sure!
是露西
It's Lucy.
她想邀我一起喝咖啡
She wants to meet for coffee.
我爱你  佩妮
I love you, Penny!
你在忙什么呢
Hey, what're you working on?
我在思考能不能借助
I'm thinking about how one could use
快速旋转镜把虚光子
the fact that a rapidly rotating mirror
转化为光子的方法
turns virtual photons into real ones
来解决吸收暗能量的问题
as a method of observing dark energy.
这主意挺有意思
That's a pretty cool idea.
是的  你来得正好
Yeah. It's great you're here.
我非常想听听工程师的意见
I'd love to get an engineer's opinion.
没问题
Sure.
我这椅子老吱吱响
This chair is squeaky.
你说我是送修还是买把新的
Now, do I fix it or get a new one?
谢尔顿  我花了一早上的时间
Well, Sheldon, it took me all morning,
终于找到了那家录像店的店主
but I found the owner of the video store.
我很高兴地宣布  他是在睡梦中平静地死去
And I am happy to report that he died peacefully in his sleep,
也就是喝醉后淹死在泳池底了
drunk at the bottom of a pool.
总之  这DVD没有地方还
Anyway, there is no one to return the DVD to,
问题圆满解决了
so this issue is resolved.
我要特别说明一点
And I'd just like to point out that
虽然这毛衣让人好不舒服
even though the sweater was uncomfortable,
我也没有以此为借口
I didn't use it as an excuse
到处顶撞周围的人
to antagonize everyone around me.
你可以把它还给录像店老板的亲戚嘛
You know, you could reimburse the video store owner's next of kin.
都说问题已经解决了
Or it's resolved!
还给亲戚这主意听上去不错
Hey, that next of kin thing sounds pretty good.
这是你掉的吧
I believe this is yours.
能问你们个问题吗
Can I ask you guys a question?
我明晚就要去见露西了
So, I'm seeing Lucy tomorrow night,
我从来没和甩掉我的人出去玩过
and I've never hung out with someone who broke up with me.
我该怎么做呢
How do you do it?
你不能让她发现你很受伤
You can't let her know you're hurting.
关键是要充满自信
You know, the key is confidence.
为什么每件事的关键都是充满自信
Why is the key always confidence?
怎么就不能是腰间赘肉啦  焦虑不安啦
How come it's never love handles and flop sweat?
如果这姑娘伤你这么深
If this girl hurt you so much,
你真的还想和她见面吗
are you sure you want to see her again?
容我说明一下
Well, if I may...
他这人自尊心几乎为零
he has so little self-respect
又极度渴望哪怕是微乎其微的爱情
and is so desperate for the smallest crumb of affection,
所以她就算在拉杰的床上
she could literally sleep with his own father
睡了他爹  还把视频发到网上
in his own bed and post the video to YouTube,
拉杰还是会送花给她
and he'd still buy her flowers
并向她求婚
and ask her to be his bride.
他说得没错
He's right.
但我的理由是  如果能通过这个考验
But in my defense, if we could survive that,
世上还有什么能把我俩分开呢
we could survive anything.
既然你真的愿意这么做
Well, if you're sure you want to do this,
反正也只是喝个咖啡而已
it's only coffee...
你就放松心态  静观其变吧
just relax and see what happens.
-那我能夸她气色不错吗  -当然
- Well, can I say she looks nice? - Sure.
能说我好想她吗
Can I tell her I miss her?
如果她问起的话  也许吧
Maybe, if she asks.
能给她看看我手绘的一幅
Oh, can I show her an oil painting I made
我和她被儿孙们环绕的油画吗
of us surrounded by our children and grandchildren?
这还是留着第二次见面时再说吧
I'd save that for the second date.
也好  也好
Good, good.
反正不管我怎么努力
'Cause no matter how hard I try,
都没法把那对双胞胎画得一模一样
I cannot get the twins to look alike.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
我在寻找那个傻逼店主的
Oh, I'm just trying to find the stupid next of kin
傻逼亲戚  好把DVD还给他们
to this stupid video store owner so I can return the DVD
好欣赏谢尔顿看到这事没烦到我时
and see the look on Sheldon's stupid face
他脸上的傻逼表情
when he sees that I didn't let this get to me.
谢尔顿又不在
Sheldon's not here.
干嘛不把毛衣脱下来
Why don't you take the sweater off?
这牵涉到原则问题
Th-Th-There's a principle at stake!
-什么原则  -我也不知道
- Which is? - Oh, I don't know.
谁管它呀  看我这一身
Who cares? Look at me!
我的天
Oh, my God!
这毛衣是用蜜蜂织的吗
Is that sweater made of bees?
快脱下来吧  我不会告诉他的
Come on, take it off. I won't tell.
不行  如果我脱下来的话  谢尔顿就赢了
No, no, honey, if I take it off, Sheldon wins.
亲爱的
Sweetie...
每天夜里你没有把他谋杀在睡梦之中时
every night you don't kill him in his sleep,
他就已经赢了
he wins.
算了...我就快成功了
Nah, I-it's... it's almost done.
我只需要找到他的亲戚
I just, I have to find...the next of kin,
把DVD寄给他们
and send 'em the DVD
然后坐等和我肤色相同的人死掉
and then just wait for someone with my complexion to die
我就可以植皮了
so I can get a skin graft.
笑一个
Smile.
你这是干嘛  拍照干嘛
What-what is that? What is that for?
你可以把它发给普林斯顿大学
So you can send it to Princeton
把你白交的学费要回来
and get your money back.
不得不说  谢尔顿
I must say, Sheldon,
这DVD的事  你处理得
you're handling this DVD business
相当成熟  令我刮目相看
with an impressive amount of maturity.
这有什么可感叹的
I don't know why that surprises you.
我本来就是个成熟的人
I'm a grown man.
我的运动夹克
As should be evident by this sport coat
和这朵逼真的胸花也证实了这一点
and very real flower in my lapel.
你是不是实践了某种新的应对机制呀
Is there some kind of new coping mechanism you're employing?
你应该问点更有趣的问题
The more interesting question you should be asking is,
比如"这朵花闻起来是什么香味呢"
"What does this flower smell like?"
我看是"可悲味"吧
I'm gonna go with sad.
所以那DVD背后有什么内幕吗
So what's the story with you and this DVD?
哪有什么内幕
There's nothing to tell.
也许是因为我买了一本书
Maybe I purchased a book entitled,
叫做《别为小事担忧》
Don't Sweat the Small Stuff
我听从了里面的睿智建议
and I followed its wise suggestions,
其中一条是
one of which was:
驻足片刻闻花香[别说了  快闻花吧]
stop and smell the flowers.
-你不是吧  -求你啦
- Seriously? - Please.
-你好  -来啦
- Hi. - Hello.
见到你我真高兴
Oh, it's so good to see you.
我也是
You, too.
请坐
Please, sit.
我帮你点了卡布奇诺
I, uh, I got you a cappuccino.
我记得这是你最喜欢的
I remembered it was your favorite.
我还点了屑饼蛋糕
I also got crumb cake,
但我想起来这是我最喜欢的  我就吃了
but I remembered it was my favorite and I ate it.
总之  你还好吗
Anyway, uh, how are you?
挺好的
I'm pretty good.
听我说  我想跟你道歉
Listen, I just wanted to apologize
我不该用一封电邮和你分手
for breaking up with you in an e-mail.
我也吃光了屑饼蛋糕
Well, and I ate all the crumb cake.
人都会犯错的嘛
we both made mistakes.
好的
Okay.
你约我出来我真是太高兴了
I'm so happy you asked me here,
希望我们改天还能再聚
and I hope we can hang out again sometime.
不论是朋友关系
You know, as friends,
还是炮友关系  都行
lovemaking partners, whatever.
其实我有对象了
I'm kind of seeing someone.
我想我知道怎么回答
I think I know the answer to this,
但还是要搞清楚  你说的不是我  对吗
but just to be clear, it's not me, right?
这全是你的错
This is all your fault!
我应该听獴狐猴的话
I should've listened to Mun-Mun
因为我一直在和
because I've been playing with a cobra
叫做佩妮的眼镜蛇玩
and her name is Penny!
你为什么这么残忍
Why are you so cruel?
看着我痛苦你很享受吗
Do you enjoy my pain?
芝士蛋糕工厂有个女生  我可以帮你介绍
There's a girl at the Cheesecake Factory I can set you up with.
我爱你  佩妮
I love you, Penny!
为什么我能将检测宇宙暗物质的
How is it I can conceptualize a methodology
方法概念化
of examining dark matter in the universe
却想不出办法修好整蛊喷水花呢
but can't figure out how to fix a novelty squirt flower?
我想真正的问题在于
I think the real question is,
你为什么要将时间浪费在廉价幼稚的恶作剧上
why do you waste your time with cheap, childish pranks?
可能有深层的原因
There's probably a deep reason.
我很乐意和你一边吃点罐子里的花生糖
Which I'd be happy to discuss with you
一边讨论这个问题
over some peanut brittle in a can.
谢尔顿  我已经没办法了
Okay, Sheldon, I am out of options!
录像带店的老板  勒西斯·曼鲁奇恩
Video store owner, Nursis Manookian,
根本就没有直系亲属
has no next of kin!
你看起来怒气冲冲的
Well, you seem hot under the collar...
是毛衣闹的吗
or is that the sweater?
不不
Oh, oh, no, no.
是因为我花了一下午时间
I-It's because I spent all afternoon
去举行他葬礼的亚美尼亚教堂调查
at the Armenian church where his funeral mass was held.
据索拉奇恩神父所说
According to Father Solakian,
没人参加葬礼
no one attended.
幸运的是  我跑这趟并不是完全浪费时间
Luckily, my trip wasn't a complete waste.
我点了根蜡烛  祈祷你快死
I lit a candle and prayed for your death.
但我不是亚美尼亚人  所以可能不管用
But I'm not Armenian, so it probably won't work!
这事结束了  对吧
This is over, right?
不一定
Oh, not necessarily.
我建议你去亚美尼亚或是黎巴嫩
I suggest you look for long-lost relatives
找找有没有失联已久的亲戚
either in Armenia or Lebanon.
听好了  谢尔顿
Listen to me, Sheldon.
我不会去黎巴嫩
I am not going to Lebanon
还《超级马里奥兄弟》的影碟
to return Super Mario Bros. the movie!
也许很好玩呢
You know, it might be fun.
反正你爱吃鹰嘴豆泥[黎巴嫩特色食品]
You love hummus.
为什么你好像不在意这事呢
Why isn't this bothering you?
你的脑袋里面不痒吗
I-Isn't your brain getting itchy?
这是你的卡借的
This is on your card.
有可能会毁了你的信用记录
This could be ruining your credit score!
为什么这事没让你发疯呢
Why isn't this making you crazy?
莱纳德
Leonard...
我有话跟你说
I have something to tell you,
但我要你保证  不许跳脚
but I want you to promise not to flip out.
什么事
What?
七年前
Seven years ago,
我发现DVD过期未还
I found out the DVD was late
已经付了钱了
and I paid for it.
什么
What?
我当时准备跟你说的
I was going to mention it at the time,
但我想  有一天
but then I thought, some day,
这件事能给你好好上一课
this might be a teachable moment.
我...你...
I... You...
怎么这样
How can...
你是不是人啊
What?!
谢尔顿
Sheldon...
你这样做太恶毒了
that was diabolical.
我知道
I know.
其实我也不容易
And it wasn't easy.
你明白等待多年却不知道
Do you have any idea what it's like to wait for years
能否得到最终的"满足"  有多痛苦吗
and never know if you're going to finally get satisfaction?
你比佩妮形容的还要漂亮
You're even prettier than Penny said.
我不敢相信你这样的女生
I can't believe a girl like you
居然没有男友
doesn't have a boyfriend.
我没有
Well, I don't.
我不相信你  你在骗我
I don't believe you, you're lying to me!
什么
What?
没关系
Oh, it's okay.
我没道德底线  我寂寞到绝望的程度
I have no morals and I'm desperately lonely.
我不介意做小三
I'll be the other man
你要一枝红杏出墙来  我会依着墙角站
if you want a little something-something on the side.
你脑子进水了吗
What is wrong with you?!